Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Files
  - Project Files
    - Novarro, Ramon - Residence
      - Specifications, correspondence, bills, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Kaitis Construction claims, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Specifications & building permits, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Contracts - preliminary, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Estimates, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Bills (1 of 3), Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Bills (2 of 3), Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Bills (3 of 3), Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 28 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Obler, Arch - Well drilling prior to residence
      - General, Project No. 126 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 126 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Legal, Project No. 126 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Bids, Project No. 126 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Contracts & agreements, Project No. 126 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Othman - Metal roof - residence
      - General, Project No. 129 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Pent-O-Rama (Sanchez) - Residence, Project No. 250
      - Doodles (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Studies & engineering calculations (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Pent-O-Rama - House, Project No. 242
      - Client notes (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Photographs (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - Clients (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - Land survey (Box 64, Folder 30)
      - Client correspondence (Box 64, Folder 31)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates (Box 64, Folder 32)
      - Quantity estimates (Box 64, Folder 33)
      - Cost estimates (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 64, Folder 35)
      - Specifications & notes (Box 64, Folder 36)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 64, Folder 37)
      - Specifications - general (1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 38)
      - Specification - general (2 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Pfeiffer, John F. - Residence, Project No. 308
      - Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Client - notes (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Photographs (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Land survey (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Architect's agreements (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Estimates (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Specifications - general (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Specifications - originals & work sheets (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Specifications - Monolithic Bermuda Roof (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Construction - clarifications (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Construction - general (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Specifications - general (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Phoenix Country Club - [Landscaping]
      - General - 1920, Project No. 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Piatigorsky, Gregor - Entrance gate, Project No. 298
      - Gate repairs & tree planting (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Piatigorsky, Gregor - Residence remodel and addition, Project No. 275
      - Client correspondence (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Land survey (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Photographs (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Hardware estimates (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Cost estimates (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Engineering estimates (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Construction - accounts & billings (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Construction - contractor / owner agreements (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Construction - hardware list (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - Contractors - releases & bills (Box 71, Folder 39)
      - Construction - bids (Box 71, Folder 40)
      - Landscaping (Box 71, Folder 41)
      - Notice of completion (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - Construction - contractors' certificates (Box 71, Folder 43)
      - Construction - contractor's vouchers (Box 71, Folder 44)
      - Construction (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Contractors - reconstruction (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Construction - materials & labor (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Desk folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Construction - sub-contractors (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Pico Robertson Mall - Mall & urban planning, Project No. 292, 323
      - Supervision journal (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - Appointment folder, 27 July 1964 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 21)
      - Clippings & photos (Box 83, Folder 22)
      - Civil defense articles & pamphlets (Box 83, Folder 23)
      - Pilot program & schematics (Box 83, Folder 24)
      - Rough notes & sketches (Box 83, Folder 25)
      - Estimates (Box 83, Folder 26)
      - FHA & city planning outlines (Box 83, Folder 27)
      - Client - report & data (Box 83, Folder 28)
      - Feasibility study (Box 83, Folder 29)
      - Preliminary data (Box 83, Folder 29)
      - General notes (Box 83, Folder 31)
      - Soil report (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Pihl, Charles - Residence & garage, Project No. 288
      - Client - correspondence (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Client - notes (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Client - photographs (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Surveys (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Specifications (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Specification notes (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Pilgrimage Play Theatre - Remodel for music concerts, Project No. 293
      - Construction - supervision journal (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Clients (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Publications & publicity (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Client - yellow notes (LW) (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Survey & notes (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - Garrett Eckbo & surveyor Sam Becken (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Cost & quantity estimates (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - Specifications & schedules (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Plan checks and reports & billing department data (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Pole, Rupert - Residence [designed by Eric Wright], Project No. 264
      - Client loan application (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Land survey (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Cost & quality estimates (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Engineering estimates (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Desk folder (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Specifications (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Construction - material bids (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Construction - bids (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Contractor / owner agreements (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Polster, Leonard - Residence, Project No. 260
      - Client correspondence (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Architect's agreements (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Land survey (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Estimates - lumber (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Estimates - calculations (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Specifications (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Construction (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Powell, L.H. - Residences
      - General, Project No. 179, 180 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Preuss - Residence
      - Bids, Project No. 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Other, Project No. 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Price, Tony - Book shop
      - General, Project No. 82 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ramona Gardens - Housing project
      - Rose Hill Courts Housing Project, Project No. 141 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 1 of 2), Project No. 141 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 2 of 2), Project No. 141 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Insuarance policy & report, Project No. 141 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Housing data, Project No. 141 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 141 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Redlich, Mr. & Mrs. Ivo P. - Residence, garage & landscaping
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - Construction photographs, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Estimates, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 34)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Construction - contractors, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - Construction - sub-contractors, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - Construction - bids, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - Bills & payroll records, Project No. 168 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Reitz, Henry - Residences, Project No. 171, 173
      - Client correspondence & notes, Project No. 171, 173 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 171, 173 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Estimates, Project No. 171, 173 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Specifications, Project No. 171, 173 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 171, 173 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Richardson, Burt - Residence
      - General, Project No. 71 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Louis - Residence #2
      - Specifications, Project No. 139 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 139 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Ruby, Harry - Residence
      - Bills, Project No. 104 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - General, Project No. 104 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Saint Luke's Presbyterian Church - Church, Project No. 273
      - Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Client notes (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Land survey (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Architect's certificates & agreements (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Specifications (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Critic's report (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Architect' studies (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - General (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - Specifications (1 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Specifications (2 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Specifications (3 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - Rough specification notes (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Supervision journal (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Desk folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Bids (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Engineer's bills (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Construction (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Samuel, Louis - Residence
      - General, Project No. 50 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 50 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Preliminary estimates, architect's contracts, permits, Project No. 50 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - General, Project No. 84 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Santa Monica High School - Open air theatre
      - General, Project No. 6 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sauer, Dr. W.E. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 90 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Schuyler, Janet Allen - Residence
      - General, Project No. 146 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Schwien, L.N. - Residence remodel
      - Client data, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - Agreements & certificates, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 31)
      - Estimates, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 32)
      - Specifications, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 33)
      - Construction, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 205 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Seeberger, Louis - Residence and garage remodel, Project No. 295
      - Correspondence & notes (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Cost estimates (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 73, Folder 38)
      - Supervision journal (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Shulman, Harold - Residence & carport
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Specifications, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Construction, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Estimates, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 203 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Sierra Madre, City of - Planting
      - unspecified, Project No. 13 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Slater, Mrs. Frank T. - Residence
      - Desk folder, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Specifications, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 210 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Mel - Residence & garage
      - Specifications, Project No. 151 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 151 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Estimates, Project No. 151 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Bids, Project No. 151 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Smith, S.R. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 88 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Warren G. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 145 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Smith, William - Residence
      - General, Project No. 115 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Solomon, Solie - Nursery School
      - Construction - sub-contractors' correspondence, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Construction - sub-contractors' certificates, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Construction - sub-contractors' agreements, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Construction - job notes, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Plan checking receipts, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Bids, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Supervision journal, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Estimates - engineering data, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Architect's agreements, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Pool, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Estimates - quantity survey, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Tower, doll house, sign, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 188 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Stein, Mr. & Mrs. Ronald - Residence, Project No. 284
      - Client - correspondence (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Declaration of restrictions & approved preliminary plans (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Supervision journal (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Owner / architect contracts (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Estimates - quantity survey (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Specifications - general (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Construction - "Alysnite" data (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Desk folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Steiner, Herman - Chess Club and office remodel, Project No. 291
      - Desk folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Office records (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Notes & cuts (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Zoning variance (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Land survey (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Cost estimates (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Estimates & costs (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Architect's agreements (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Duplicates (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Statement of account, July 1962 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Statement of account, September 1962 - chess club (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Client correspondence (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Sub-contractors - materials, bids & billings (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Construction - estimates & cost of completion (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Construction - bids, contracts & correspondence (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Construction - permits & plan checks (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Entrance portico (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Stendahl, Earl - Candy factory, Project No. 160
      - Candy kitchen, Project No. 160 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Stendahl, Earl - Gallery remodel and additions, Project No. 160
      - General, Project No. 160 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Stendahl, Earl - Residence
      - General, Project No. 131 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Swann, Harold - Residence
      - General, Project No. 122 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Taggart, Martha - Residence
      - Additions & alterations, Project No. 7 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - General, Project No. 7 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Specifications, reconditioning costs - 1957, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Specifications, plot plans, contract agreements, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Bills, supervision, estimates, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - 1924 remodel (1 of 2), Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - 1924 remodel (2 of 2), Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - 2623 Harcourt residence (L.A.), Mrs. Wright, Mrs. Cutter, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - 1976 restoration estimates, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Insurance policies, 1970's, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Trust deeds - 1970's, Project No. 7 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Thanksgiving Square - Civic park, Project No. 345
      - General (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence - Residence & furniture
      - Data & drawings, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Specifications, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Statments, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Furniture, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - General, Project No. 58 & 59 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence - Residence, Project No. 58 & 59
      - General (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Tibbett, Mrs. Grace - Residence alterations
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 125 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Specifications, Project No. 125 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Tibbett, Mrs. Jane - House sketch
      - General, Project No. 174 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Todd-A.O. - Theatre, Project No. 304
      - Client - correspondence (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Century City master plan (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Notes & cuts (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Brochures (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - Client notes (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Supervision journal (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Tomer, George - Residence - preliminary drawings, Project No. 350
      - General (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Triangle Park - Shopping center remodel, Project No. 336
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Outline specifications (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Construction - billings paid (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Construction (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Job notes (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Notes & photos (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Map (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Material for deposition (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Material for deposition (2 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Tule Mat House - Desert home
      - General, Project No. 79 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Turtelotte, W.D. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 144 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - University Club - Landscaping
      - General, Project No. 5 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara - Japanese exhibit, Project No. 326
      - Supervision journal (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Upham, Frank - Residence
      - unspecified, Project No. 46 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Van Benthuysen - Remodel
      - General, Project No. 110 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Vidor, Charles - Residence
      - General, Project No. 111 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Wagner, Gordon P. - Residence
      - Desk folder, Project No. 232 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Weber, W.J. - Residence
      - (1 of 2), Project No. 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (2 of 2), Project No. 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Welton, James - Remodel
      - Job notes & sketches, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 35)
      - Grading, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 36)
      - Notice of completion, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 37)
      - Door hardware, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 38)
      - Construction - pool, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 39)
      - Construction - contractor's correspondence, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 40)
      - Construction - contractor's certificates, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 41)
      - Construction - contractor's vouchers, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 42)
      - General, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 43)
      - Fence, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 44)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 45)
      - Applications & permits, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 46)
      - Specifications for remodel, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 47)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 48)
      - Client - correspondence, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 49)
      - Client - notes, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 50)
      - Air conditioning, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 51)
      - Construction - contractor's / owner's agreements, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 52)
      - Construction - bids, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 53)
      - Construction - general, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 54)
      - Land survey, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 55)
      - Architect / owner contracts, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 56)
      - Certificates, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 57)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 58)
      - Estimates - Engineering & structural calculations, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 59)
      - Specifications, Project No. 335 (Box 57, Folder 60)
    - Westfair Shopping Center [Martin / Fann] - Shopping Center, Project No. 330
      - Supervision journal through 8 Oct. 1970 (Box 83, Folder 34)
      - Specifications - Thrifty Drug Store (Box 83, Folder 35)
      - Specifications - Safeway (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 36)
      - Specifications - Safeway (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 37)
      - Land survey (Box 83, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Client - notes (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Photos (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Client meeting (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Client - publicity (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Land survey (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - Construction - bids (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 84, Folder 19)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 84, Folder 20)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 84, Folder 21)
      - Site plan - modifications (Box 84, Folder 22)
      - Design criteria (Box 84, Folder 23)
      - Paul Fitting - letters and data (Box 84, Folder 24)
      - Preliminary agreement and data (Box 84, Folder 25)
      - Outline - specifications (Box 84, Folder 26)
      - Specifications (Box 84, Folder 27)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 84, Folder 28)
      - Client correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 29)